Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Small, A. W. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1923 May 22; 1p
  - Small, Maynard and Co. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 May 5
  - Smathers, W. W. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 18; 1p
  - Smedley, Agnes (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 31; 1p
    - Enc.: Boas (to Wilson), 1919 July 31
    - To Boas, 1919 July 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 28; 1p
  - Smidowitch, P. (Box 83)
    - To Nansen, F., 1927 Oct. 27
  - Smith (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1902 May 19
    - To Boas, 1902 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
    - From Teit, J. H., 1912 Feb. 8
  - Smith, A. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 2p
  - Smith, A. J. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep.
  - Smith, Alice (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 2
  - Smith, Allan H. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 24; 1p
  - Smith, Barry C. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Smith, Benjamin E. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 May 25
  - Smith, Bernard (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 8; 1p
  - Smith, C. Alphonso (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 15
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p
  - Smith, Charles S. (Box 83)
    - see Schwab, G.H., 1906 May 26
  - Smith, D. E. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 22; 1p
  - Smith, Mrs. David M. (Box 83)
    - To Razovsky, C., 1938 July 22; 1p
  - Smith, de Cost (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1888 Sep. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 July 30
    - Smith, Mrs. Douglas, 1936 Jan. 9
  - Smith, Ester (Box 83)
    Inuit family
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 May 23
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 18
  - Smith, Edward P. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1916 May 19
  - Smith, Edward R. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 10
  - Smith, F. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 10; 2p
  - Smith, Gerald B. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1918 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 21; 1p
  - Smith, G. Elliott (Box 83)
    - 1934 Sep. 5, 2p
    - 1935 Nov. 7, 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 8; 2p
  - Smith, Gretta (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 21; 1p
      Enc: List on Civ. of W. Hemisphere
  - Smith, H. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1928 July 20; 1p
  - Smith, H. De Busk (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr.; 2p
    - From Espinosa, A.M., 1920 Apr. 26; 1p
  - Smith, Harlan I. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1894 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 May 27
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5
    - From Boas, 1910 May 12
    - From Boas, 1910 June 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1886 July 8
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 3
    - undated letter: early Apr., 1894 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 3
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1896 July 10
    - To Boas, 1896 July 13
    - To Boas, 1896 July 17
    - To Boas, 1896 July 22
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1902 May 19; 3p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1902 July 12; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1902 Aug. 22; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1905 July 5
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1905 Aug. 6
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1908 Sep. 14
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1908 Sep. 25
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1908 Oct. 16
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1909 Mar. 16; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1910 Jan. 10
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1910 Feb. 5
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1910 Feb. 19
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1910 Mar. 23
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1910 Mar. 31
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1910 June 3
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1911 June 18; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1911 June 23
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1912 Apr. 17; 7p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1912 Sep. 9; 3p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1913 May 21; 4p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1913 Aug. 9; 6p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1914 Feb. 14; 4p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1914 Feb. 23; 6p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1915 May 12; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1915 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1915 Sep. 27; 4p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1916 Dec. 23
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1918 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 2p
    - To Mrs. Boas, 1938 July 8; 2p
    - From Rideout, H. M., 1910 Aug. 1
    - From Hodge, F. W., 1914 Mar. 7
    - To Mrs. Sophie Boas, 1902 July 12; 2p
    - To Teit, J.A., 1907 Apr. 23; 2p
    - To Rideout, H.M., 1910 Aug. 9
  - Smith, H. W. (Herbert) (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 9; 1p
  - Smith, Irwin (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Duggan, Stephen P., 1920 June 24; 1p
  - Smith, J. R. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 25; 1p
  - Smith, James H. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 25; 1p
  - Smith, Jessica (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Sep. 30; 1p
  - Smith, John M. Powis (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 6; 1p
    - From McFarland, A. C., 1920 Aug. 23; 1p
  - Smith, Kaj Birket (Box 83)
    see Birket-Smith, K.
  - Smith, Liv. V. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1924 May 20; 1p
    - Enc. with Smith, L.V. (to Jackson, G.P.), 1924 May 27
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 3; 1p
    - To Jackson, G.P., 1924 May 27; 3p
    - Enc. with Jackson, G.P., 1924 May 31
  - Smith, M. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 25; 5p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 May 11
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - From James, E.J., 1909 Feb. 2
  - Smith, M. B. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1922 Sep. 29; 1p
  - Smith, Marian (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 8; 1p
  - Smith, Mary Fraser (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 1; 1p
  - Smith, Monroe (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1908 May. 11; 2p
  - Smith, O. W. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 14; 2p
  - Smith, Phillip S. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p
  - Smith, Reed (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 22; 1p
  - Smith, R. E. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1920 June 28; 1p
  - Smith, R. R. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Smith, Robert C. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Smith, S. (Box 83)
    - To Esquire S. S. Keppel, 1906 Aug. 27
  - Smith, S. W. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 10; 1p
  - Smith, T. P. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Smith, W. L. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 12; 2p
  - Smith, W. W. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 28
  - Smith, William (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 14
  - Smith, William A. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 24
  - Smith, William C. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 26
  - Smith Subscription Co. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep.
  - Smithers, A. E. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 19
  - Smithers, Herlinda G. (Box 83)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1912, 4p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1912
  - Smithsonian Institute (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 20; 1p
      See Walcott, C. D.
  - Smithsonian Institute Bureau of Anthropology (Box 83)
    - From Lowman, C. L., 1919 July 12
    - Enc. with Lowman, C. L., 1919 July 13
  - Smithsonian Institute Bureau of Ethnology (Box 83)
    - 1927, 2p
      See Swanton, John R.
  - Smithsonian Institute Bureau of Exchanges (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 30; 1p
  - Smithsonian Institute Bureau of International Exchanges (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 8; 1p
  - Smoot, R. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 8; 1p
  - Smutny, Adele (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 6; 1p
  - Smutny, Joseph (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1897 June 15; 4p
  - Sneath, E. Hershey (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 14; 1p
  - Snelling, W. O. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 31; 1p
  - Sniton, H. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
  - Snoddy, J. M. (Box 83)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 24
  - Snow, William (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 2; 1p
  - Snyder, M. I. (Box 83)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 15
  - Sobel, N. R. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Sobernheim, M. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 2p
  - Social Science research council (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 26; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1928, 1930 June 24; 2p
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1928, 2p
    - see Ogburn, W.F., 1929 May 31
  - Social Science Research Council Committee on Fellowships (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 13; 1p
  - Social Science Research Council Committee on Grants in Aid (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p
  - Social Sciences Abstracts (Box 84)
    See Chapin, F. Stuart
    - Social Sciences Abstracts
    - Found at end of June 1928
  - Social Scientific Society of New York (Box 84)
    See Glogau, Otto
  - Societé d'Anthropologie de Paris, 1859-1909 (Box 84)
    - To President of Columbia Univ., 1908 Dec. 19
  - Societé d'Etnnographie de Paris (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; 1p
  - Societé des Nations (Box 84)
    - From Folkierski, W., 1928 Oct. 13
    - In Schrijnen, J., 1928 Oct. 25
  - Society for Ethical Cultures of New York (Box 84)
    See Adler, Felix
  - Sock, P. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 3; 1p
  - Soier, Loisl (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; 2p
    - Found at end of 1920
  - Sola Pool, D. de (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 6; 1p
  - Solalinde, A. G. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 12; 1p
  - Solash, I. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 14; 1p
  - Solberg, A. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 11
  - Solberg, T. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 14
  - Solmsen, F. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 6; 1p
    - To Dunn, L. C., 1934 June 24; 1p
    - Enc. Career and Schriften Norden, E. (open letter), 1934 June 24
    - Jaeger, W. -- (open letter), 1934 June 19
    - see Jaeger, W. (open letter), 1934 June 19
    - Enc. with Solmsen, F., 1934 June 24
  - Sologuren (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - see Boas, F. (to Engerrand, G.C.), 1913 Oct. 31
  - Solow, H. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 28; 1p
  - Sombart, W. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1906 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 20; 3p
  - Somerndike, J. M. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 5; 1p
  - Sommerfeld, Martin (Box 84)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1933, 2p
  - Sommerfelt, Alf (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 July 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 11; 1p
  - Sommers, David (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 18; 1p
    - Enc: Amer. Committee for Anti-Mazi literature, 1936 May 11
    - To Boas, 1936 May 19; 1p
    - Enc: Amer. Comm. for Anti-Nazi literature., 1936 May 18
  - Sondern, F. E. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1921 May 13; 1p
  - Soringer, J. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 2p
  - Sorkin, M. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 21; 1p
  - Sorley, W. R. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 June 6; 2p
  - Soskin, William (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 25; 1p
  - Soubeiran, J. L. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 30; 1p
  - Soule, George (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 11
  - Soule, Gordon A. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 12; 1p
  - Sound Specialties Company (Box 84)
    See Thompson, Lincoln
  - Soustelle, J. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 18; 1p
  - Southall, James P. C. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 2; 1p
  - Southard, P. J. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 20; 1p
  - Spain (Box 84)
    - Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain Found at end of Feb. 1938, ons microfilm
      Open letter on culture....in Spain. Replies.
  - Spain. Ministerio de Propaganda (Box 84)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1937, 8p
  - Spain, Santander (Box 84)
    - From Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1937
  - Spanish Embassy, Jan. 1937 (Box 84)
  - Spanish Intellectual Aid (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 29; 1p
  - Spannarts, L. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 6; 1p
  - Sparkes, Grace M. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 27; 1p
  - Speak-O-Phone Recording Studios (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 6; 1p
  - Speck, Frank G. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1905 June 3
    - From Boas, 1905 June 12
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1915 May 6
    - see Boas, F. (to Gordon, G.B.), 1916 May 22
    - see Boas, F. (to Dixon, R.B.), 1916 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1929, 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 July 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 July 29
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 28; 1p
    - Fpund at end of Apr. 1927, 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 8; 1p
    - On margin of Boas, F. (to Speck, F.G.) Found at end of, 1929 Dec.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To H.A. Andrews, 1912 June 26
    - To Eishberg, M., 1934 May 15; 1p
    - From Shoemaker, H. W., 1924 June 2
  - Speck von Sternburg (Box 84)
    See Sternburg, Speck von
  - Speed, F. G. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 15
  - Speer, Robert E. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 16; 1p
  - Speer, Robert K. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas
    - see Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain Replies, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 17; 1p
  - Speers, J. M. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 4
  - Speers, W. F. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
  - Spencer, Anna G. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 12
    - To Boas, 1905 June 12
  - Spencer, E. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p
    - see Boas, F. (to Tyler, J.M.), 1919 Nov. 13
  - Spencer, H. E. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 8
  - Spencer, J. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 30; 2p
  - Spencer, Louise C. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Spencer, M. L. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 27; 2p
  - Spencer, Nelson S. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1910 June 4
    - From Boas, 1910 June 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 June 6
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 May 15
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Jacobi, A., 1911 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Feb. 18
    - From Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Feb. 22
    - From Kelsey, F. W., 1911 Mar. 2
    - From Knapp, Charles, 1911 Jan. 13
  - Spencer, Theodore (Box 84)
    - To Boas
    - see Wiener, Philip Paul, 1938 Nov. 30
  - Spencer, W. B. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Spender, Ordway and Wierum (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1911 June 2
  - Spengler, Otto (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 19; 2p
  - Speranza, C. L. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 13; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 16
  - Sperni, Guiseppi (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Spero, Sterling D. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 27; 1p
    - Enc. re, 1936 Feb. 5; 1p
    - Thalheimer, A.
  - Sperry, A. B. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 2; 1p
  - Spetzier, K. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1933 May 12; 1p
  - Speyer, James (Box 84)
    - From Boas, F. & Heuser, F. W. J., 1920 July 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 July 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p
    - see Boas, F. (to Klenze, C.V.), 1920 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 2p
    - see letter dated Oct. 4, 1933 to Warburg, Mrs. Paul to Boas., 1933 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 25; 1p